Alisina Adeel

asina8403@gmail.com, Address: 110 Kellys Way the Blue Mountains, ON, L9Y 0L6

Proficiency Summery

I worked as a font-end web developer at GAOTek for four months, In addition, I build several websites with WordPress, React.js and next.js as a freelancer. Please take a look to my updated portfolio here: https://portfilio-alisina-adeel.vercel.app/

Skills

- HTML, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript
- React Js, Next Js, Typescript
- Node Js, Git, GitHub

- Problem Solving
- Troubleshooting and Debug
- Work ethnic

Work History

Front-end Web developer at <u>Bright Maker Weave</u> / Islamabad, Pakistan

03/2024-03/2023

- Meeting with clients to discuss website design and function
- Designing and building the website front-end.
- Creating the website architecture
- Generating WordPress themes and plugins
- Troubleshooting content issues

Website: https://brightmakerweave.com

Front-end Web developer at \underline{GAOTek} / Online

01/2023-04/2023

- Design, develop, test and deploy design features in a timely manner
- Collaborated with project managers to successfully deliver projects on time
- Successfully debugged the web-related issues, leading to improved efficiency and performance.

Other-related web project as freelancer

- 1-Space-Portfolio https://alisina-adeel.vercel.app/
- 2- Cursor-animation https://cursor-animation-swart.vercel.app/
- 3-Local-Restaurant

Education

<u>Kateb University</u> - Kabul, Afghanistan / 2017 - 2022 Bachelor Degree - Computer Science

Hobbies

- Playing Game
- Write to Code
- Reading and Learning
- Music and Fitness
- Travelling
- Photography

Speak, Read and Write

- English
- Dari
- Persian / Farsi